# LAUREN CHEN

DIGITAL MARKETING SPECIALIST

## CONTACT

- (123) 456-7890
- lauren.chen@mail.com
- 47 W 13th St, New York, NY 10011
- lauren.chen.com
- in linkedin.com/in/lauren.chen
- twitter.com/lauren-chen

## SUMMARY

Digital Marketing Specialist with 6+ years of experience in online marketing, branding, and business strategy across music, media, and entertainment industries. Skilled in evaluating financial needs and implementing multi-pronged digital strategies that increase revenue and drive brand growth.

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

January 2019 - Present

# **Digital Marketing Specialist**

Triangle Music Group, New York, NY

- Manage digital sales and streaming accounts to improve brand positioning and growth
- Source and develop new strategic partnerships, social engagements, and advertising opportunities that generate new revenue streams
- Collaborate with internal departments to execute national advertising campaigns, plan global digital distribution, and re-deploy a 1M+ consumer sales and marketing database

January 2018 - January 2019

#### Digital Marketing Associate

Momo Software, New York, NY

- Worked with management to develop and apply digital marketing plans with a focus on driving acquisition and conversion
- Devised and implemented robust digital acquisition plans, ensuring precision in financial reporting, budgets, and forecasts
- Increased conversions by 15% from paid sources (PPC, Grant, Display, and VOD)

January 2017 - January 2018

# Marketing Intern

Kingston Digital, New York, NY

- Helped research, write, and edit blog posts for Kingston's website
- Determined relevant keywords and entities for pages using Semrush, Ahrefs, and Page Optimizer Pro
- Gathered and analyzed data from social media PPE campaigns

#### **EDUCATION**

May 2017

#### **Bachelor of Arts, Communications**

New York University, New York, NY

## SKILLS

- Digital Data Analytics
- Adobe Photoshop
- Digital Marketing
- Adobe Illustrator